[
    { "id": "H_001", "front": "Europäische Union", "back": "Brüssel" },
    { "id": "H_002", "front": "Afrikanische Union", "back": "Addis Abeba" },
    { "id": "H_003", "front": "Verband Südostasiatischer Nationen", "back": "Jakarta" },
    { "id": "H_004", "front": "Union Südamerikanischer Nationen", "back": "Quito" },
    { "id": "H_005", "front": "Abchasien", "back": "Sochumi" },
    { "id": "H_006", "front": "Afghanistan", "back": "Kabul" },
    { "id": "H_007", "front": "Ägypten", "back": "Kairo" },
    { "id": "H_009", "front": "Albanien", "back": "Tirana" },
    { "id": "H_010", "front": "Algerien", "back": "Algier" },
    { "id": "H_011", "front": "Andorra", "back": "Andorra la Vella" },
    { "id": "H_012", "front": "Angola", "back": "Luanda" },
    { "id": "H_013", "front": "Antigua und Barbuda", "back": "Saint John’s" },
    { "id": "H_014", "front": "Äquatorialguinea", "back": "Malabo" },
    { "id": "H_015", "front": "Argentinien", "back": "Buenos Aires" },
    { "id": "H_018", "front": "Armenien", "back": "Jerewan" },
    { "id": "H_019", "front": "Aserbaidschan", "back": "Baku" },
    { "id": "H_020", "front": "Äthiopien", "back": "Addis Abeba" },
    { "id": "H_021", "front": "Australien", "back": "Canberra" },
    { "id": "H_022", "front": "Bahamas", "back": "Nassau" },
    { "id": "H_023", "front": "Bahrain", "back": "Manama" },
    { "id": "H_024", "front": "Bangladesch", "back": "Dhaka" },
    { "id": "H_025", "front": "Barbados", "back": "Bridgetown" },
    { "id": "H_026", "front": "Belgien", "back": "Brüssel" },
    { "id": "H_027", "front": "Belize", "back": "Belmopan" },
    { "id": "H_028", "front": "Benin", "back": "Porto Novo" },
    { "id": "H_029", "front": "Bergkarabach", "back": "Stepanakert" },
    { "id": "H_030", "front": "Bhutan", "back": "Thimphu" },
    { "id": "H_031", "front": "Bolivien", "back": "Sucre" },
    { "id": "H_032", "front": "Bosnien und Herzegowina", "back": "Sarajevo" },
    { "id": "H_033", "front": "Botswana", "back": "Gaborone" },
    { "id": "H_034", "front": "Brasilien", "back": "Brasília" },
    { "id": "H_035", "front": "Brunei", "back": "Bandar Seri Begawan" },
    { "id": "H_036", "front": "Bulgarien", "back": "Sofia" },
    { "id": "H_037", "front": "Burkina Faso", "back": "Ouagadougou" },
    { "id": "H_038", "front": "Burundi", "back": "Bujumbura" },
    { "id": "H_039", "front": "Chile", "back": "Santiago de Chile" },
    { "id": "H_040", "front": "Republik China", "back": "Taipeh" },
    { "id": "H_041", "front": "Volksrepublik China", "back": "Peking" },
    { "id": "H_044", "front": "Cookinseln", "back": "Avarua" },
    { "id": "H_045", "front": "Costa Rica", "back": "San José" },
    { "id": "H_046", "front": "Dänemark", "back": "Kopenhagen" },
    { "id": "H_050", "front": "Deutschland", "back": "Berlin" },
    { "id": "H_051", "front": "Dominica", "back": "Roseau" },
    { "id": "H_052", "front": "Dominikanische Republik", "back": "Santo Domingo" },
    { "id": "H_053", "front": "Dschibuti", "back": "Dschibuti-Stadt" },
    { "id": "H_054", "front": "Ecuador", "back": "Quito" },
    { "id": "H_055", "front": "El Salvador", "back": "San Salvador" },
    { "id": "H_056", "front": "Elfenbeinküste", "back": "Yamoussoukro" },
    { "id": "H_057", "front": "Eritrea", "back": "Asmara" },
    { "id": "H_058", "front": "Estland", "back": "Tallinn" },
    { "id": "H_059", "front": "Fidschi", "back": "Suva" },
    { "id": "H_060", "front": "Finnland", "back": "Helsinki" },
    { "id": "H_061", "front": "Frankreich", "back": "Paris" },
    { "id": "H_063", "front": "Gabun", "back": "Libreville" },
    { "id": "H_064", "front": "Gambia", "back": "Banjul" },
    { "id": "H_065", "front": "Georgien", "back": "Tiflis" },
    { "id": "H_067", "front": "Ghana", "back": "Accra" },
    { "id": "H_068", "front": "Grenada", "back": "St. George’s" },
    { "id": "H_069", "front": "Griechenland", "back": "Athen" },
    { "id": "H_070", "front": "Guatemala", "back": "Guatemala-Stadt" },
    { "id": "H_071", "front": "Guinea", "back": "Conakry" },
    { "id": "H_072", "front": "Guinea-Bissau", "back": "Bissau" },
    { "id": "H_073", "front": "Guyana", "back": "Georgetown" },
    { "id": "H_074", "front": "Haiti", "back": "Port-au-Prince" },
    { "id": "H_075", "front": "Honduras", "back": "Tegucigalpa" },
    { "id": "H_076", "front": "Indien", "back": "Neu-Delhi" },
    { "id": "H_078", "front": "Indonesien", "back": "Jakarta" },
    { "id": "H_079", "front": "Irak", "back": "Bagdad" },
    { "id": "H_080", "front": "Iran", "back": "Teheran" },
    { "id": "H_081", "front": "Irland", "back": "Dublin" },
    { "id": "H_082", "front": "Island", "back": "Reykjavík" },
    { "id": "H_083", "front": "Israel", "back": "Jerusalem" },
    { "id": "H_085", "front": "Italien", "back": "Rom" },
    { "id": "H_086", "front": "Jamaika", "back": "Kingston" },
    { "id": "H_087", "front": "Japan", "back": "Tokio" },
    { "id": "H_088", "front": "Jemen", "back": "Sanaa" },
    { "id": "H_089", "front": "Jordanien", "back": "Amman" },
    { "id": "H_090", "front": "Kambodscha", "back": "Phnom Penh" },
    { "id": "H_091", "front": "Kamerun", "back": "Yaoundé" },
    { "id": "H_092", "front": "Kanada", "back": "Ottawa" },
    { "id": "H_093", "front": "Kap Verde", "back": "Praia" },
    { "id": "H_094", "front": "Kasachstan", "back": "Astana" },
    { "id": "H_095", "front": "Katar", "back": "Doha" },
    { "id": "H_096", "front": "Kenia", "back": "Nairobi" },
    { "id": "H_097", "front": "Kirgisistan", "back": "Bischkek" },
    { "id": "H_098", "front": "Kiribati", "back": "South Tarawa" },
    { "id": "H_099", "front": "Kolumbien", "back": "Bogotá" },
    { "id": "H_100", "front": "Komoren", "back": "Moroni" },
    { "id": "H_101", "front": "Kongo, Demokratische Republik", "back": "Kinshasa" },
    { "id": "H_102", "front": "Kongo, Republik", "back": "Brazzaville" },
    { "id": "H_103", "front": "Korea, Nord", "back": "Pjöngjang" },
    { "id": "H_104", "front": "Korea, Süd", "back": "Seoul" },
    { "id": "H_105", "front": "Kosovo", "back": "Prishtina" },
    { "id": "H_106", "front": "Kroatien", "back": "Zagreb" },
    { "id": "H_108", "front": "Kuba", "back": "Havanna" },
    { "id": "H_109", "front": "Kuwait", "back": "Kuwait-Stadt" },
    { "id": "H_110", "front": "Laos", "back": "Vientiane" },
    { "id": "H_111", "front": "Lesotho", "back": "Maseru" },
    { "id": "H_112", "front": "Lettland", "back": "Riga" },
    { "id": "H_113", "front": "Libanon", "back": "Beirut" },
    { "id": "H_114", "front": "Liberia", "back": "Monrovia" },
    { "id": "H_115", "front": "Libyen", "back": "Tripolis" },
    { "id": "H_116", "front": "Liechtenstein", "back": "Vaduz" },
    { "id": "H_117", "front": "Litauen", "back": "Vilnius" },
    { "id": "H_119", "front": "Luxemburg", "back": "Luxemburg" },
    { "id": "H_120", "front": "Madagaskar", "back": "Antananarivo" },
    { "id": "H_121", "front": "Malawi", "back": "Lilongwe" },
    { "id": "H_122", "front": "Malaysia", "back": "Kuala Lumpur" },
    { "id": "H_123", "front": "Malediven", "back": "Malé" },
    { "id": "H_124", "front": "Mali", "back": "Bamako" },
    { "id": "H_125", "front": "Malta", "back": "Valletta" },
    { "id": "H_126", "front": "Marokko", "back": "Rabat" },
    { "id": "H_128", "front": "Marshallinseln", "back": "Majuro" },
    { "id": "H_129", "front": "Mauretanien", "back": "Nouakchott" },
    { "id": "H_130", "front": "Mauritius", "back": "Port Louis" },
    { "id": "H_131", "front": "Mazedonien", "back": "Skopje" },
    { "id": "H_132", "front": "Mexiko", "back": "Mexiko-Stadt" },
    { "id": "H_133", "front": "Mikronesien", "back": "Palikir" },
    { "id": "H_134", "front": "Moldawien", "back": "Chișinău" },
    { "id": "H_136", "front": "Monaco", "back": "Stadtstaat" },
    { "id": "H_137", "front": "Mongolei", "back": "Ulaanbaatar" },
    { "id": "H_138", "front": "Montenegro", "back": "Podgorica" },
    { "id": "H_139", "front": "Mosambik", "back": "Maputo" },
    { "id": "H_140", "front": "Myanmar", "back": "Naypyidaw" },
    { "id": "H_141", "front": "Namibia", "back": "Windhoek" },
    { "id": "H_142", "front": "Nauru", "back": "Yaren" },
    { "id": "H_143", "front": "Nepal", "back": "Kathmandu" },
    { "id": "H_144", "front": "Neuseeland", "back": "Wellington" },
    { "id": "H_145", "front": "Nicaragua", "back": "Managua" },
    { "id": "H_146", "front": "Königreich der Niederlande", "back": "Amsterdam" },
    { "id": "H_148", "front": "Niger", "back": "Niamey" },
    { "id": "H_149", "front": "Nigeria", "back": "Abuja" },
    { "id": "H_150", "front": "Niue", "back": "Alofi" },
    { "id": "H_151", "front": "Nordzypern", "back": "Lefkosa" },
    { "id": "H_152", "front": "Norwegen", "back": "Oslo" },
    { "id": "H_154", "front": "Oman", "back": "Maskat" },
    { "id": "H_155", "front": "Österreich", "back": "Wien" },
    { "id": "H_156", "front": "Osttimor / Timor-Leste", "back": "Dili" },
    { "id": "H_157", "front": "Pakistan", "back": "Islamabad" },
    { "id": "H_159", "front": "Palästina", "back": "Ostjerusalem (Gaza und Ramallah)" },
    { "id": "H_160", "front": "Palau", "back": "Melekeok" },
    { "id": "H_161", "front": "Panama", "back": "Panama-Stadt" },
    { "id": "H_162", "front": "Papua-Neuguinea", "back": "Port Moresby" },
    { "id": "H_163", "front": "Paraguay", "back": "Asunción" },
    { "id": "H_164", "front": "Peru", "back": "Lima" },
    { "id": "H_165", "front": "Philippinen", "back": "Manila" },
    { "id": "H_166", "front": "Polen", "back": "Warschau" },
    { "id": "H_167", "front": "Portugal", "back": "Lissabon" },
    { "id": "H_168", "front": "Ruanda", "back": "Kigali" },
    { "id": "H_169", "front": "Rumänien", "back": "Bukarest" },
    { "id": "H_170", "front": "Russland", "back": "Moskau" },
    { "id": "H_171", "front": "Salomonen", "back": "Honiara" },
    { "id": "H_172", "front": "Sambia", "back": "Lusaka" },
    { "id": "H_173", "front": "Samoa", "back": "Apia" },
    { "id": "H_174", "front": "San Marino", "back": "San Marino" },
    { "id": "H_175", "front": "São Tomé und Príncipe", "back": "São Tomé" },
    { "id": "H_176", "front": "Saudi-Arabien", "back": "Riad" },
    { "id": "H_177", "front": "Schweden", "back": "Stockholm" },
    { "id": "H_178", "front": "Schweiz", "back": "Bern" },
    { "id": "H_179", "front": "Senegal", "back": "Dakar" },
    { "id": "H_180", "front": "Serbien", "back": "Belgrad" },
    { "id": "H_182", "front": "Seychellen", "back": "Victoria" },
    { "id": "H_183", "front": "Sierra Leone", "back": "Freetown" },
    { "id": "H_184", "front": "Simbabwe", "back": "Harare" },
    { "id": "H_185", "front": "Singapur", "back": "Stadtstaat" },
    { "id": "H_186", "front": "Slowakei", "back": "Bratislava" },
    { "id": "H_188", "front": "Slowenien", "back": "Ljubljana" },
    { "id": "H_190", "front": "Somalia", "back": "Mogadischu" },
    { "id": "H_192", "front": "Somaliland", "back": "Hargeysa" },
    { "id": "H_193", "front": "Spanien", "back": "Madrid" },
    { "id": "H_194", "front": "Sri Lanka", "back": "Colombo" },
    { "id": "H_195", "front": "St. Kitts und Nevis", "back": "Basseterre" },
    { "id": "H_196", "front": "St. Lucia", "back": "Castries" },
    { "id": "H_197", "front": "St. Vincent und die Grenadinen", "back": "Kingstown" },
    { "id": "H_198", "front": "Südafrika", "back": "Pretoria" },
    { "id": "H_199", "front": "Sudan", "back": "Khartum" },
    { "id": "H_200", "front": "Südossetien", "back": "Zchinwali" },
    { "id": "H_201", "front": "Südsudan", "back": "Juba" },
    { "id": "H_202", "front": "Suriname", "back": "Paramaribo" },
    { "id": "H_203", "front": "Swasiland", "back": "Mbabane" },
    { "id": "H_204", "front": "Syrien", "back": "Damaskus" },
    { "id": "H_206", "front": "Tadschikistan", "back": "Duschanbe" },
    { "id": "H_207", "front": "Tansania", "back": "Dodoma" },
    { "id": "H_208", "front": "Thailand", "back": "Bangkok" },
    { "id": "H_209", "front": "Togo", "back": "Lomé" },
    { "id": "H_210", "front": "Tonga", "back": "Nukuʻalofa" },
    { "id": "H_211", "front": "Transnistrien", "back": "Tiraspol" },
    { "id": "H_212", "front": "Trinidad und Tobago", "back": "Port of Spain" },
    { "id": "H_213", "front": "Tschad", "back": "N’Djamena" },
    { "id": "H_214", "front": "Tschechien", "back": "Prag" },
    { "id": "H_215", "front": "Tunesien", "back": "Tunis" },
    { "id": "H_216", "front": "Türkei", "back": "Ankara" },
    { "id": "H_217", "front": "Turkmenistan", "back": "Aschgabad" },
    { "id": "H_218", "front": "Tuvalu", "back": "Funafuti" },
    { "id": "H_219", "front": "Uganda", "back": "Kampala" },
    { "id": "H_220", "front": "Ukraine", "back": "Kiew" },
    { "id": "H_221", "front": "Ungarn", "back": "Budapest" },
    { "id": "H_222", "front": "Uruguay", "back": "Montevideo" },
    { "id": "H_223", "front": "Usbekistan", "back": "Taschkent" },
    { "id": "H_224", "front": "Vanuatu", "back": "Port Vila" },
    { "id": "H_225", "front": "Vatikanstadt", "back": "Stadtstaat" },
    { "id": "H_226", "front": "Venezuela", "back": "Caracas" },
    { "id": "H_227", "front": "Vereinigte Arabische Emirate", "back": "Abu Dhabi" },
    { "id": "H_228", "front": "Vereinigte Staaten", "back": "Washington, D.C." },
    { "id": "H_230", "front": "Vereinigtes Königreich", "back": "London" },
    { "id": "H_232", "front": "Vietnam", "back": "Hanoi" },
    { "id": "H_233", "front": "Weißrussland", "back": "Minsk" },
    { "id": "H_234", "front": "Westsahara", "back": "El Aaiún" },
    { "id": "H_235", "front": "Zentralafrikanische Republik", "back": "Bangui" },
    { "id": "H_236", "front": "Zypern", "back": "Nikosia" }
]